hi spring fans welcome to another
嗨，春季粉丝们欢迎来到另一个
special installment of spring tips this
弹簧的特别分期提示
is yet another sort of midseason
是另一种中期
interregnum episode of spring tips
春季小隔间发作
because I want to bring to you something
因为我想带给你一些东西
that's very exciting that just dropped a
刚刚放下一个
master on Spring Framework which is the
掌握Spring框架
web NBC not FN programming model so if
网络NBC不是FN编程模型，所以如果
you've ever used the spring web flux
您曾经使用过弹簧卷材助焊剂
function reactive end point style that's
功能反应终点样式
now available for a spring and receive
现在可用于春季并接收
based applications servlet based
基于应用的servlet
applications and it's it's not a
应用程序，这不是
reactive thing is just for spring MVC
反应性的东西只是为春季MVC
right it is the it's an equivalent or an
对，这是等效或
analogue to the address controller style
与地址控制器样式类似
but for spring MVC which is super cool
但是对于春季MVC来说，这是非常酷的
right and this is possible of course
对，这当然是可能的
because Spring Framework and spring MVC
因为Spring框架和spring MVC
with it all assume a java baseline and
所有这些都假设一个Java基线，
so when we introduced the function
所以当我们介绍该功能时
reactive sort of DSL for spring webflix
用于春季webflix的DSL响应式
people really liked it and one common
人们真的很喜欢它，还有一个共同点
sort of request was that this would be
有点要求是
made available for spring MVC
可用于春季MVC
applications as well and that's now
应用程序，现在
happening it's on master I would love
发生在我愿意的主人身上
for you to all try it out and we're
给大家尝试一下，我们
gonna go ahead and introduce some of
继续介绍一些
those features here today and this and
今天的功能以及
this look at the new stuff so in order
这是为了看新东西
to get it of course we have to use the
要获得它，我们当然必须使用
latest and greatest spring boot which in
最新最好的 spring boot
turn brings in the latest greatest
转身带来最新的最
spring MVC web let me see FN I'm just
Spring MVC网站让我看到FN我只是
gonna bring in the web stuff web support
会带来网络内容的网络支持
I'll bring in Lombok and dev tools and
我将带上Lombok和开发工具，
that's it you know you can bring in
就这样，你知道你可以带来
whatever else want you can use APA and
任何其他想要您可以使用APA和
you know JDBC you know these are the
你知道JDBC，你知道这些是
things it is just a regular spring MVC
事情只是常规的MVC
application it's just that we're using a
应用程序，只是我们正在使用
different programming model so we're
不同的编程模型，所以我们
gonna hit generate and by default this
将点击生成，默认情况下，
will result in a tomcat based
将导致基于tomcat
application I'm gonna change that out
应用程序，我将改变它
I'm going to swap out Tomcat and use
我将换出Tomcat并使用
undertow although you could use jetty or
尽管可以使用码头或
Tomcat or you know any configuration you
Tomcat或您知道任何配置
could even you know
你甚至知道吗
harkening back to the servlet deployment
回到servlet部署
options spring tip that I did a a few
我做了一些的春季选项
years ago now you can even turn this
年前，现在你甚至可以把这个
into a dot waar and deploy it to
到一个点阵并将其部署到
traditional web server traditional
传统的Web服务器传统的
servlet container all these are fine
servlet容器都很好
choices good choices right lots of
选择好选择对很多
options so let's go to our build
选项，让我们开始构建
I'll be using Java 11 thank you
我将使用Java 11谢谢
and I want to bring in undertow okay I'm
而且我想带上我，我
gonna exclude Tomcat Tomcat
将会排除Tomcat Tomcat
okay spring boots starter the Tomcat ID
好的， spring boot 启动器的Tomcat ID
okay so there's my exclusion and so in
好吧，所以我被排除在外了
every way this is just a basic
每种方式这只是一个基本
application just go ahead and just start
应用程序就可以开始
it up like so get going
像这样开始吧
now I'm gonna use some of the nice new
现在我要使用一些不错的新
properties that are inside of a spring
弹簧内部的属性
boot you know I had with posit or ease
开机，你知道我有正负
that you use this I don't have these
你用这个我没有这些
properties so doesn't matter but I don't
属性无关紧要，但我不
have I don't have KP on the class method
我在类方法上没有KP吗
but if I did that's what I'd be using
但是如果我做到了，那就是我会用的
okay so we start
好吧，我们开始
okay so now let's see what this looks
好吧，现在让我们看看它的外观
like so let's say I've got class product
就像这样，假设我有一流的产品
all right and private or actually better
没事，私下或实际上更好
yet person okay so private string name
还可以的人，所以私有字符串名称
private long ID at data at all are its
数据中的私有长ID完全是它的
no args constructor right just basic
没有args构造函数，只是基本的
stuff right nothing fancy here and want
东西没什么好看的，想要
to create a class person service private
创建私人的班级服务
final set person people set of new
最终集人新人集
person one gene to Josh
乔什的第一人称基因
three for Tammy
塔米的三个
alright so there's a few names here and
好了，所以这里有几个名字
no no I can't leave that exceeding the
不，不，我不能离开那超出
merchant I just can't fill web wouldn't
我只是无法填补网络的商人不会
approve so okay good now we have that
批准好吧好，现在我们有了
set person
设定人
oh okay so just a very simple set of end
哦，好吧，这只是一组非常简单的结尾
points here person by ID and in
通过ID和in指向此处的人
retrospect I'm wishing I had just used
回顾我希望我曾经用过
spring data JPA but you know such as
spring data JPA，但您知道诸如
life filter P P get ID that equals ID
生活过滤器PP获得的ID等于ID
that find first or else throw you know
首先找到否则扔你知道
illegal argument exception okay you know
非法论点例外好吗你知道
person
人
doctor good name look at that ID all
医生好名字都看那个身份证
right so there's this okay so this is
对，所以这可以，所以这是
just a very simple service now we can
只是一个非常简单的服务，现在我们可以
create our endpoint okay we can create
创建我们的端点好了，我们可以创建
our endpoint centrally like this we're
这样我们的端点集中
using the function reactive style but
使用功能反应风格，但
it's not it's not reactive it's just a
不是不是没有反应这只是一个
functional style so web a b c FN style
功能样式，因此网络abc FN样式
right so router function server responds
正确，因此路由器功能服务器会做出响应
routes and use the builder so there's
路线并使用建造者，所以
two builders in the function reactive
反应性函数中的两个构建器
style right one is to say router
风格对吧，就是说路由器
function
功能
routes or that route and then put
路线或那条路线，然后放
request me to get like this and a
要求我得到这样的
handler function at this
处理程序功能
and you can even change it together too
你甚至可以一起改变它
and route you know post or whatever
并路由您知道的帖子或其他内容
right you can do all that kind stuff
对，你可以做所有类似的事情
that all still works but that's also
一切仍然有效，但这也是
been I think superseded by this this
被我认为已经被这个
other style which I quite like called
我非常喜欢的另一种风格
route so you can say round dodging you
路线，所以你可以说回避你
know is the Builder there bring that in
知道那里的建设者带来了
and I can say okay people I provided you
我可以说我提供给您的人很好
hinder function and then you build the
阻碍功能，然后您建立
whole thing right to build okay and so
整个事情都可以建立，好吧，等等
the job here is to injected person
这里的工作是注射人
service PS okay so I'm gonna provide a
服务PS好的，我要提供一个
server response time okay it up body and
服务器响应时间可以了
notice that for the body parameter I
请注意，对于身体参数I
don't have to specify a counselor all
不必全部指定顾问
right
对
in fact there's no need to specify that
实际上，无需指定
all because unlike in there they spin
都是因为它们不像在那儿旋转
web flex we world where I'm returning a
web flex我们在世界上返回的地方
publisher of type T where T is going to
T将要转到的类型T的发布者
be consumed as a stream over time and
随着时间流逝而被消耗掉，
thus I can't assume that I have the
因此我不能认为我有
whole body of the the publisher you know
您认识的出版商的整体
I can't pass the whole thing into JSON
我无法将整个内容传递给JSON
to tax on for Jason marshalling here I'm
为Jason编组在这里纳税
gonna pass the whole thing the whole
将整个事情传递
body I send Mac is in mystic past you
我发送Mac的身体已经过去了
know in one fell swoop to the to the
知道一个人扑向了
message converter they should be message
消息转换器，他们应该是消息
converter and so it can figure out what
转换器，所以它可以找出什么
you know it's it's not gonna try to
你知道那是不会尝试的
figure out what each stand days it's
弄清楚每个站立的日子
just kind of figure out the whole thing
只是弄清楚整个事情
so PS dot all okay clean this up a
所以PS点都可以了
little bit replace it with that replace
一点点替换为那个替换
that the lambda use static imports and
Lambda使用静态导入，并且
voila okay so there's my functional sort
瞧，好，这是我的功能分类
of web flex style or web flex that FN
Web柔性样式或FN的Web柔性
style endpoint except that it's not web
样式终结点，但不是网络
blocks right so let's see that in action
正确阻止，让我们看看实际情况
here I'm going to recompile 0.6 seconds
在这里，我将重新编译0.6秒
to see the things start up point people
看到事情开始点人
okay so there's my application sample
好，所以有我的申请样本
data good that's working just fine let's
可以正常工作的数据好，让我们
say I want to cut another end point that
说我想削减另一个终点
gives me the data by it's the ID right
通过ID给我数据
so ID
所以ID
are okay doc body PS defined by ID here
在这里由ID定义的文档正文PS可以吗
I want to get access to the path
我想获得路径
variable so I say are the path variable
变量，所以我说是路径变量
ID and turn this into a long alright
ID并将其转变为长期可用
same as before rebuilt okay point two
与重建前一样好点二
five nine seconds - there's that three
五九秒-那是三
four etc right so it's very easy to make
四个等，所以很容易制作
changes this is just a server I assist a
更改这只是我协助的服务器
webserver and of course all this time
网络服务器，当然一直都在
you can see I've been using undertow
你可以看到我一直在使用underwow
right here's X and IO where's the
就在这里X和IO在哪里
undertow packages so all that's there I
包底下的东西，所以我在那里
know it's just a regular servlet
知道这只是一个普通的servlet
container like I said I could package
像我说的我可以包装的容器
this up as a dot war it's a trunk so you
这是一场点战，它是树干，所以你
know this is a good example of of
知道这是一个很好的例子
reading and of course you can do it
阅读，当然你可以做到
thing so you can say okay I want to add
事情，所以你可以说好，我想添加
so person save person in all right
这样人就可以救人
and what I do want to say this stuff
我想说些什么
people dot add new person you don't get
人点添加您不认识的新人
name and I guess I want to do privately
名字，我想我想私下做
final atomic long
最终原子长
counter equals zero tonic long and here
计数器等于零补品长，这里
I should have done this temperature
我应该做这个温度
touch increment or get an increment
触摸增量或获得增量
okay okay so there we are
好吧好吧，所以我们在那里
okay
好的
no database not a very good database at
没有数据库不是一个很好的数据库
all but hey you know probably that
所有人，但嘿，你可能知道
should be synchronized okay so we've got
应该同步好了，所以我们有
that now we're going to add a post
现在我们要添加一个帖子
endpoint post people and here break this
端点发布人，在这里打破这个
out into a full-on lambda I'm going to
进入完整的lambda，我要
say give me the body of the incoming
说给我来的身体
request as a as a as a person right I
作为一个人的要求我
can take person incoming
可以带人来
but for status bar and I'll say give me
但是对于状态栏，我会说给我
the name of our name and I'll say PR
我们名字的名字，我会说公关
don't save or PS to save new person okay
不要保存或PS以保存新人，好吗
and our result equals and then I'm gonna
我们的结果等于然后我要
send that back so I'm gonna create a new
发送回去，所以我要创建一个新的
you were on you were at a crate is
你在，你在一个箱子里
people /id so result get ID okay
人员/ id，因此结果获得ID即可
Oh URI and finally our mature response
哦，URI，最后是我们成熟的回应
it's also so response doc created awry
这也是响应文档创建错误的原因
and pass in the result good stuff look
并传递结果好看的东西
at that ok so this could be cleaned up a
这样就可以清理了
bit I imagine and in fact this could be
我想像一下，实际上这可能是
clean up as well so hard up body person
这么好清理身体的人
dot class okay so there's our actual
点类好，所以我们有实际的
code you don't need this so that's our
代码，您不需要这个，这就是我们的
post endpoint and you can see you can't
发布端点，您可以看到您无法
eat you can do all sorts of interesting
吃，你可以做各种有趣的事
things here you can add you know it's
您可以在这里添加的东西，您知道它是
just it's exactly expect but notice that
只是完全期望，但请注意
word we're attaching things to the
一句话，我们把东西附在
Builder object here all right I've got a
这里的Builder对象好吧，我有一个
builder to which I'm adding these
我要添加这些的构建器
endpoints and I'm then come build well I
端点，然后我就可以很好地构建
can do you know I can say okay well if
你知道吗我可以说好
math.random greater than point five then
那么math.random大于第5点
and only then do I want to add something
然后才想添加一些东西
to Aidid have close to it whatever it
到艾迪德（Aidid）都接近它
right I can do dynamic things for
我可以做一些动态的事情
programmatic I can read configuration
程序化我可以读取配置
from a database I can read from a config
从数据库中，我可以从配置中读取
file or something I can respond to some
文件或其他我可以回应的内容
external thing right I don't have to add
正确的外部事物，我不必添加
it through my spring MVC style
通过我的春季MVC风格
annotations and we'll see what I mean by
注释，我们将明白我的意思
that in a second here so it's we start
一秒钟在这里，这是我们开始
this
这个
okay so let's try and send some data
好吧，让我们尝试发送一些数据
curl minus H content type application
卷曲减去H含量类型的应用
Jason - yeah it should be little close
杰森-是的，应该有点接近
to 880 or such people
到880左右
name equals Bob all right error oh I
名字等于鲍勃好吧错误哦
didn't did I restart
我没有重启
just restart maybe the dev tools I'm
重新启动也许是我的开发工具
working
工作中
problem so that's localhost:8080 people
问题，所以这是本地主机：8080人
sees out an immutable collection of
看到一个不变的集合
course this so new - Center and I want
当然如此新-中心，我想要
the initial data to come from there we
最初的数据来自那里我们
start
开始
okay there we go so if I had Bob again
好吧，我们去吧，如果我又有了鲍勃
you can see we're incrementing it's
你可以看到我们正在增加它
being added so now I go back to the
被添加，所以现在我回到
browser go here people there we are
浏览器去这里的人在那里
there's our five and six we got two
我们有五个和六个，我们有两个
different bobs now what if I want to you
现在不同的鲍勃如果我要你怎么办
know mix and match right I mentioned
知道我提到过的混搭
spring MVC style so that you can still
春天的MVC风格，使您仍然可以
do that is this a spring MVC application
这样做是Spring MVC应用程序
right so that's controller hello we
好的，那是控制器你好，我们
built that
建立
nope being
不存在
just restart that
只是重新启动
okay
好的
but you can't seem to mix and match I've
但你似乎无法混合搭配
got that now I go to people so I can
现在我去找人，所以我可以
share you know I can easily take my
分享，你知道我可以轻松带走我的
existing application but if he's
现有的应用程序，但如果他是
bringing me C style controllers or
带给我C风格的控制器或
springing me C controller srini and then
让我弹起C控制器srini，然后
gradually add web you know web MVC dot F
逐渐添加网站，您知道网站MVC点F
M style endpoints here and that's great
M样式的端点在这里，很棒
because I mean I can take advantage of
因为我的意思是我可以利用
my existing business logic all of it was
我现有的业务逻辑全是
built on top of the sermons back and I
建立在布道后面，我
can use this new style without having to
可以使用这种新样式，而不必
sort of do all at once migration right I
一次完成全部迁移对吧，我
don't I can use things I can reuse
我不能用我可以重用的东西
things piece panel and this is after all
东西一块面板，这毕竟是
at the end of the day a servlet
在一天结束时，一个servlet
application right I am running on top of
我正在运行的应用程序权
the stove a container so for example if
在炉子上放一个容器，例如
I look at this I can say oh well give me
我看着这个我可以说哦，好吧，给我
the servlet request well there it is
servlet请求很好
right there playing it should be serving
就在那里玩应该服务
requests and I can do whatever I want
请求，我可以做我想做的一切
with that you know get the on type of
这样你就知道了
the context map of cookies or whatever
Cookie或任何其他内容的上下文映射
all this stuff is just as before and if
所有这些东西和以前一样，如果
you want it there it's it's it's there
你想要它在那里它就是那里
we're not trying to hide that at all
我们根本没有试图隐藏它
it's just a more convenient yes out so
只是更方便了，所以
when do you use which well as always the
您什么时候会像往常一样使用
same the same is true for spring web
春季网同样如此
flex you can use the functional sort of
flex您可以使用功能性的
style if you want to have all the
风格，如果你想拥有所有
routing in one place right like this
这样路由到一个地方
I've got routing here I've also got the
我在这里路由，我也有
handler logic here and we'll talk about
这里的处理程序逻辑，我们将讨论
that in a second but the routing is here
一秒钟，但路由在这里
it's all in one place whereas here the
都在一个地方，而这里
routing the matching you know that
路由匹配，您知道
predicates are screwing about the code
谓词搞砸了代码
base and in the different packages in
基础和在不同的包中
which you find rest controllers or
您可以找到 rest controller 或
controllers so it's nice to be able to
控制器，所以很高兴能够
centralize all that here the other thing
将所有其他东西集中在这里
is if you want to control what gets
是如果您想控制得到什么
registered dynamically right here I can
我可以在这里动态注册
decide based on some external condition
根据某些外部条件决定
whether to register something or not
是否注册某些东西
whereas this is you know once you define
而一旦您定义
the method it's very hard to sort of
这种方法很难分类
undo that or not register the method you
撤消或不注册您的方法
have to just comment it out in the code
只需在代码中将其注释掉
there's nobody easily dynamically
动态地没有人
registered things at runtime um
在运行时注册的东西
now go back to this code
现在回到此代码
this is not so bad here it's not so bad
这还不错，这里还不错
either
要么
but here that's a there's three lines of
但是这里有三行
code and start to complicate and search
代码并开始复杂化和搜索
the muddy this matter function so very
浑浊的这个物质功能是如此非常
common pattern here is to create a
这里的常见模式是创建一个
handler so a person handler it's not up
处理程序，所以一个人处理程序不起来
particular step there's not a specific
特定的步骤没有特定的
stereotype in spring called a handler
春天的刻板印象称为处理程序
it's not a tender or anything like that
这不是温柔的或类似的东西
but the way it works is you you you know
但是它的运作方式就是你你知道
you remember this handler function here
你还记得这里的处理函数
it's a functional interface so implement
这是一个功能性的界面，因此请实施
handler function server response and
处理程序功能服务器响应和
that's the contract and then you can
那是合同，那么你可以
just get rid of this part here and that
只是在这里摆脱这部分
and there you go
然后你去
so I say handle get all reservations
所以我说把所有的保留
okay
好的
good here sir response dot and what we
好的，先生回应点以及我们
want to do is same as before I'm going
想做的和我要去之前一样
to extract out for example the this
提取例如这个
logic here actually the first one we're
逻辑实际上我们是第一个
to do is uh this one so they're just be
要做的是这个，所以他们只是
here
这里
Arif at work I need to inject the person
我需要在工作中向他人灌输
repository person service I suppose for
我想为资料库人服务
some service good stuff and just
一些服务的好东西，只是
delegate now you can use method
现在可以使用方法委托
references so the benefit of this
参考，所以这样做的好处
approach is that you get the the best of
方法是，您将获得最好的
both world to get the routing in one
两个世界都可以将路由合二为一
place but you get the business logic in
的地方，但你得到业务逻辑
separate isolated to you know easily
隔离很容易就知道
tested things and you don't muddy the
测试过的东西，你不会糊涂
code right until pH and I'll get all
直到pH值，我都会得到所有代码
reservations and just use a method
保留，只是使用一种方法
reference this one same thing right so
引用同一件事吧
and I'll get reservation by ID take that
我会凭身份证预订的
and of course are
当然是
[Music]
[音乐]
good
好
person service alright and don't get all
人事服务还不错
get reservations by Adi okay and then
得到阿迪的预定，然后
finally the post which is you know again
最后是你再次知道的帖子
we're just kidding we're just doing Java
我们只是在开玩笑，我们只是在做Java
rules here and you have to have a method
规则在这里，你必须有一个方法
that can be functionally substituted for
可以在功能上代替
the loan or single non abstract method
贷款或单一非抽象方法
on a functional interface and that's
在功能界面上，那是
what I'm doing here so the final one is
我在这里做什么，所以最后一个是
proposed or creative person order a
建议或创意人命令
handle post person
处理职位的人
all right
好吧
good
好
and this one extract this out
而这个将其提取出来
okay so pH and I'll post person good
好吧，pH值，我会把人贴好
good stuff okay so now it's much cleaner
好东西好，现在更干净了
you can see I've got the routes I've got
你可以看到我有路线
the the handler logic agent command
处理程序逻辑代理命令
click on this to get to it's at
点击这个去它在
something and so a big deal even if it
东西，即使它很大
isn't a separate record pay code engage
不是单独的记录支付代码
your separate separate package but now
您单独的单独包装，但现在
you could also about all the logic of
您还可以了解所有逻辑
all the routing logic so try to change
所有路由逻辑，因此请尝试更改
it you know farm route people's by
你知道人们的农场路线吗
whatever well of course there's no
当然好了没有
reason you couldn't do that right
原因你做不到
because they route because this
因为他们路由，因为这
okay so not bad not bad dog let's get
好吧，还不错，不错，狗也不错
rid of that of course but you could um
当然可以，但是你可以
now let's see you start that we've got
现在让我们开始看看
our application it's working one of the
我们的应用程序正在工作之一
nice things about being top out the
关于登顶的美好的事情
cervix because you can be use all that
宫颈，因为您可以使用所有
business logic so let's just make sure
业务逻辑，所以让我们确保
everything is working there we go to
一切正常，我们去
post
发布
all right there's Bob Bob okay so that's
好吧，鲍勃·鲍勃好吧，那是
working now we can we use our existing
现在工作，我们可以使用现有的
infrastructure as well so remember all
基础设施也要记住
the things you did before in the servlet
您之前在servlet中所做的事情
API and then in spring ABC those
API，然后在春季ABC中
continue to work so in class simple
继续工作，所以上课简单
filter extends generic filter and I'm
过滤器扩展了通用过滤器，我
just gonna create a servlet filter just
只是要创建一个servlet过滤器而已
a regular filter that spring Poupon
定期弹出Poupon的过滤器
turned into service as a circle to
转为服务于
registration beam and you can directly
注册光束，您可以直接
register filters that way as well but
同样注册过滤器，但是
you know this will get tender for me
你知道这对我会变嫩
okay so entering
好的，所以进入
go to chain that to filter request okay
去链条过滤请求好吗
Xing now that's the spring MVC filter in
Xing现在是Spring MVC过滤器
serve the filter style but you can also
提供过滤器样式，但您也可以
use you can also hang filters off the
使用您还可以将过滤器挂在
router function itself just as it just
路由器功能本身就像它一样
doesn't spring whip flex so here you
没有弹簧鞭弯曲所以在这里你
know same basic approach if you
知道相同的基本方法，如果你
understand the first one then this is
了解第一个，那么这是
natural
自然
logging out the information I'm doing is
注销我正在做的信息是
I'm logging out the information so log
我正在注销信息，因此请登录
and drink
和饮料
okay try
好吧尝试
water info exiting all right
水信息退出一切正常
basic filter so let intensive to UM hand
基本的过滤器，因此让您精通UM
out of course
当然不对
restart we'll see which ones get invoked
重新启动，我们将看到哪些被调用
first I think you'll find that the
首先，我认为您会发现
servlet filter this full-service filter
Servlet过滤器此全方位服务过滤器
gets invoked before the filter may hang
在过滤器挂起之前被调用
off the router function so whatever here
关闭路由器功能，所以无论在这里
tez entering simple filter that's the
进入简单的过滤器是
thing here the servant filter and then
事情在这里，仆人过滤，然后
entering the handler filter function and
输入处理程序过滤器功能，然后
then exiting to Henderson to function
然后离开亨德森去工作
right and then finally and exiting the
对，然后最后退出
simple filter so the generic Charlotte
简单的过滤器，所以通用的夏洛特
filter wraps the nested felt to this
过滤器将嵌套的毛毡包裹到此
attached to the router function which is
附加到路由器功能
very convenient okay so again all the
非常方便，所以再次
things you know about still continue to
您所知道的事情仍然继续
work you can reuse existing risk
您可以重用现有风险的工作
controllers you can co-locate them
控制器，您可以将它们放在一起
you've got this nice DSL that doesn't
你有这个不错的DSL
abstract away or hide anything to do
摘掉或隐藏任何事情
with this or blue speck if you really
如果你真的有这个或蓝色斑点
need it to get access to the servo
需要它来访问伺服
request from each each request if you
每个请求中的一个请求，如果您
register filters and register servlets
注册过滤器并注册servlet
and we use them just as before and of
我们像以前一样使用它们
course these can be deployed to any sort
当然这些可以部署到任何种类
of a container I I swapped out Tomcat to
II的容器替换了Tomcat
undertow and I could have packaged this
知道了，我本来可以打包的
as a dot Warren deployed it to a server
作为一个点，沃伦将其部署到服务器上
container that way as well whatever your
那样的容器，无论您的
prerogative this gives you a lot of
特权给你很多
flexibility and I really hope you'll try
灵活性，我真的希望您能尝试
it out and give it a spin and let us
出来试试吧，让我们
know what you like and what you don't
知道你喜欢什么，不喜欢什么
you want to see him what you don't and
你想见他你不知道的
with that my friends as always thanks
一如既往地感谢我的朋友们
for watching and we'll see you next time
观看，我们下次见
you
您